Mateo Perez

♣ Profile

Software and industrial engineer student at Universidad de Los Andes. I have worked for the past 2 years on projects as a front-end developer. I'm currently a junior dev with ReactJs. However, I have experience with other languages and tools like Java, Py (Django-Rest), GraphQL, Mongo, MySQL, Next.Js, Apollo

Employment History

Fronted-Dev at Amcon Insitu, Bogotá

December 2019 - September 2020

I was hired as a frontend dev in December of 2019 to develop the digitization process of a company

FullStack and Entrepeneur at mimenu.com.co, Bogotá

June 2020 — Present

mimenu.com.co is a personal project I which I'm working on with 2 more teammates. Our goal is to digitize all restaurants operations in Bogota and Latam

Education

Software Engineer, Universidad de Los Andes, Bogotá January 2018 — Present

Industrial Engineer, Universidad de Los Andes, Bogotá

January 2018 — Present

Details

3144183191

mateoperez0508@gmail.com

Links

https://github.com/Mateo-P

Skills

Communication

Hard Working

Computer Skills

Leadership Skills

Fast Learner

Languages

English

Spanish; Castilian

Hobbies

Learning new programming skills, read, have fun with friends